ezanga.com 2018-12-15

# Privacy Policy | eZanga.com, Inc.

Updated: May 2018

eZanga.com, Inc. ("eZanga") is a digital marketing and ad fraud prevention company that strives to provide excellent customer service and transparency to our advertisers, customers, and users engaging with advertising from our clients. Your privacy is very important to us. As such, this Privacy Policy explains how and what information is collected or used to create and maintain eZanga services for use by our clients across all platform offerings and what choices you have in respect to your information.

 **Commitment to Privacy:**

Protecting our customers' information is of the utmost importance to us as is maintaining compliance with any governing authority to which the processing of personal information may occur for any of our product lines. The European Union ("EU") maintains strict privacy laws through General Data Privacy Regulation ("GDPR"). This standard differs significantly from U.S. law. eZanga complies with regulations where it applies to the processing of personal data, the disclosure of the appropriate notifications, and, where applicable, with provision of a process by which an individual can request the erasure of personal information.

 **What Information Do We Collect?**

eZanga may employ different methods for collecting information about those that visit our Internet properties directly, or if our platform is used by clients for the prevention of ad fraud.

From Clients: eZanga’s clients include businesses, networks, agencies, publishers, and advertisers, and we do collect personal information to identify the client to an account. The collection of this information is on a lawful basis, to which consent has been expressly given, and is part of eZanga’s normal business practices. Advertisers, businesses, or their representatives will be asked to provide personal information through the signup and registration process. This information is used to communicate the status of an account or billing and may include, but is not limited to: name, phone number, email address, website name, and address.

Technologies such as cookies, tags, and scripts are used by eZanga and our marketing partners, affiliates, analytics, and/or third-party administrators. These technologies are used to analyze trends and to gain demographic information about the user. We may receive and provide dashboard analytics based on the use of these technologies by these companies on a non-personally identifiable individual as well as an aggregated basis.

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs.

When using the eZanga Network, clients may enter third-party personal information on the platform, such as entering another user's email. This information is only used to provide the clients access to the system and not for any other purpose.

Methods of collection may include:

  *  **Cookies:**

A "cookie" is a small file that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. This enables us to store user preferences, settings, track trends, protect against fraud, and monitor search patterns. A cookie aggregates non-personally identifiable information about the visitors to our website. A cookie does not collect personally identifiable information that is unique to you, such as credit card numbers, bank accounts, social security numbers, home addresses, email addresses, and other personal information.

We use non-personally identifiable cookies to improve the quality of eZanga’s services and to better understand how users interact with us. We do not and cannot use cookies to retrieve individual, personally identifiable, information about you from your computer unless you knowingly and willingly provided such information.

The cookie technology cannot obtain information from your hard drive or pass on a computer virus. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some eZanga.com features or services may not function properly without cookies.

If you want to learn more about cookies, or how to control or delete them, please visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for additional information.

 **Phone Services:**

eZanga offers pay per call marketing with unique telephone numbers to be used on websites, emails, mobile, and offline promotions. This enables eZanga and our clients to use information about what a consumer was viewing when they made the phone call and aids in personalizing the customer experience.

eZanga may also collect information from third-party databases that includes geographic location of the caller when such information is available. This information remains anonymous and can be used to optimize our marketing and product development initiatives in order to provide a better user and client experience.

eZanga may also use third-party services or technology for the recordings, transcriptions, or analysis of phone calls and recorded information. In the event that eZanga records a call on behalf of a client, eZanga will ensure that call participants are advised of the existence and intent of the recording in a manner consistent with applicable state and federal laws. eZanga is not responsible in any way for the accuracy and validity of the content of any such recordings, and takes no steps to evaluate such accuracy or validity.

eZanga strongly encourages responsible marketing practices and the share of information for all clients and their partners. The collection, use, and disclosure of information by clients and their partners are subject to their own respective privacy policies. These policies may differ from eZanga’s policy.

 **Pixels/Web Beacons:**

eZanga uses third-party applications throughout our website which do rely on pixels, or a tiny image embedded on the web page that allows us to know you have seen the page. They also allow us to create, update, and read our own cookies.

 **Device IDs:**

A Device ID (device identification) is a distinctive number associated with a smartphone or similar handheld device. Device IDs are accessible by Publishers and can be passed to eZanga with a request. These Device IDs do not enable eZanga to identify individuals, but rather can be used for certain advertising purposes. They can be used to limit the number of times a specific advertisement is presented to the same device and to track a device to show that the device interacted with an ad (i.e. "clicked" on it, watched a video ad, or downloaded an application as a result of an advertisement). If eZanga stores a Device ID, it would be for these advertising or administrative purposes, and would not be used to create profiles of end-users over time. eZanga may also partner with third parties that have their own methods of identifying a device. These can be used as described above, or in some cases can be used for the purpose of supporting third-party targeted advertising solutions. Where these solutions are employed, eZanga will work with our Exchanges or otherwise endeavor to provide end-users with the ability to opt-out of these solutions.

 **Why Does eZanga Collect This Information?**

eZanga collects some anonymous information each time you visit eZanga.com, so we can improve the overall quality of your online experience. We also collect IP address, referral data, and browser and platform type for the purposes of preventing fraud. We do not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information with express consent.

eZanga assigns an anonymous ID number to your requests and links the following additional data to that number: the date and time you visited eZanga.com, TrafficAdvisors.com or Anura.io and the links upon which you chose to click. Like most standard website servers, we use log files to collect and store this anonymous user information. We analyze this information to examine trends, prevent fraud, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. eZanga.com may present links in a format that enables us to understand whether they have been followed. We use this information to understand and improve the content of eZanga.com.

eZanga may also develop statistical user profiles of generic consumer needs and interests by collecting both internet browsing and online purchase data, along with phone user information. This improves our audience targeting and therefore our core products. Some eZanga services may use marketing technology to allow advertisers to supplement non-personally-identifying demographic information, such as age, gender, area code, or ZIP code, to the non-identifiable profile data.

 **Does eZanga Share User Information With Others?**

We may share aggregated general information about our site with our corporate partners or clients. Examples of this include the daily number of unique visitors or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Aggregated data does not contain any personally identifiable information that could be used to contact or identify you.

We may share personally identifying information to which we have been given express consent to process or for an overriding legitimate interest to other companies or individuals in any of the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your express consent.
  * We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * When required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a criminal investigation, a court order, or legal process served on our Website. We may also share your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of eZanga.com's terms of use for any of our platform offerings, or as otherwise required by law.
  * If you have an AdPad, Traffic Advisors, or Anura account, we may share the information submitted under your account among all of our services in order to provide you with a seamless experience and to improve the quality of our services. We will not disclose your account information to other people or non-affiliated companies, except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy or with your consent.
  * We may store and process personal information collected on our site in any other country in which eZanga.com or our agents maintain facilities. By reading and accepting this Policy, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities, including those located outside your country.
  * eZanga.com may use third-party service providers to serve ads and emails on our behalf. These companies meet our supplier privacy requirements and may use technologies to measure the effectiveness of ads and emails and use information about your visits to eZanga.com so that we can provide a better experience to you. For this purpose, we may also provide these third-party service providers anonymous information about your site navigation. Some of those third parties may use this information to tailor advertising to your interests.
  * We may share certain information about you with carefully selected business partners, including those who may offer services that complement those provided by us or which we believe may be of interest to you. We may also disclose information to third parties who assist us in providing our services to you. For example, we may engage third-parties to make improvements on our site, to offer new products, and to allow us to customize your experience on the site.

 **Can a Consumer Opt-Out of Providing Information?**

eZanga uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out

<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

With regard to phone services, consumers are able to submit their phone number to the “do not call” registries. eZanga will use all efforts to observe ‘do not call’ registries in any call campaign. However, consumers who have opted-in to receive such messages, either with a client or by way of third party, shall not be subject to any ‘do not call’ restrictions. Consumers may also request personal information data erasure by emailing [privacy@ezanga.com](mailto:privacy@ezanga.com). 

**Correspondence:**

If you contact eZanga.com, we may keep a record of that correspondence, and we may collect your email address in accordance to our Retention Policy.

 **Can a Consumer Access the Personal Information Acquired by eZanga?**

While eZanga’s services are not directed towards individual consumers, there may be a need to view, erase, and/or provide the personal information eZanga holds about an individual. This information can be corrected or updated by contacting [privacy@ezanga.com](mailto:privacy@ezanga.com). For the deletion and erasure of personal information, email [privacy@ezanga.com](mailto:privacy@ezanga.com) to begin the process and we will respond to your request within 30 days.

 **How Does eZanga Use Our Clients’ Information?**

eZanga may collect information from clients for administrative needs, such as accounting and performance reporting or for the prevention of fraud. eZanga may also use the clients’ information to communicate via email newsletters or other avenues to offer product updates, information, and other communications to assist in business-related activities. Clients can opt-out from future communications by clicking on the unsubscribe links located at the bottom of such emails. In addition, any individual may request to have their personal information removed from our network by emailing [privacy@ezanga.com](mailto:privacy@ezanga.com).

It’s important to note that under the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 (15 U.S.C. § 7001), an advertiser is required to provide an opt-out mechanism for consumers to unsubscribe from future emails from the advertiser. eZanga is committed to proper Internet practices and full compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act. It is eZanga’s policy to prohibit the sending of unsolicited or ‘spam’ email by eZanga or any of our strategic partnerships, subsidiaries, or alliances.

Unless otherwise stated, eZanga keeps all personal information provided by our clients in strict confidence and treats such data with the same level of care and respect that eZanga treats their own proprietary information. eZanga may from time to time provide certain third-party administrative vendors information to run administrative or program services. Some examples of this use include, but are not limited to: email service providers, marketing automation providers, and client relationship management providers. Any third-party vendor engaging with eZanga for any form of information or services has agreed to protect the confidentiality of information provided by eZanga.

eZanga may share information when requested to comply with law enforcement towards a response to a subpoena, bankruptcy proceeding, or similar legal process. eZanga will apply the Terms of Service and other agreements to protect the rights, property, or safety of eZanga or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud and ad fraud protection.

eZanga may also share information in connection with the sale, merger, change of control, transfer of a key asset, consolidation, reorganization, or liquidation in part or whole of eZanga. In this case, clients will be notified via a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership. This will declare what, if any, aspects of the clients’ personal information was transferred, as well as any choices clients have regarding their personal information.

 **Can a Client Opt-Out of Providing Information to eZanga?**

eZanga’s primary intent in collecting information is for administrative purposes and is required as part of doing business with us. However, eZanga may periodically use collected information for marketing and communication purposes targeted towards our clients. Clients who wish to not receive such communications may opt-out before setting up an account by not granting consent (essentially “not opting in”) or at any time by contacting their eZanga account manager, in writing, or by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the promotional communications.

eZanga will send service-related email announcements on occasion when it is necessary to do so.

If you are an eZanga client, and would like the personal information eZanga holds about you to be corrected or updated please contact [privacy@ezanga.com](mailto:privacy@ezanga.com). For the deletion and erasure of personal information, email [privacy@ezanga.com](mailto:privacy@ezanga.com) to begin the process and we will respond to your request within 30 days.

 **General**

 **Public Forums:**

eZanga’s website offers publicly accessible articles and access to community social media forums, and some of this content is syndicated on other websites. Any eZanga user should be aware that any information provided in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others that have access to or read these sites. Any comments made on those websites or social media forums fall under the dictation of each of those respective privacy policies. To request removal of any personal information from an eZanga article or other community forum, contact [support@ezanga.com](mailto:support@ezanga.com) and eZanga will forward the request to the appropriate entity.

 **Social Media Widgets:**

eZanga’s corporate website ([www.ezanga.com](http://www.ezanga.com/)) or [anura.io](https://www.anura.io/) includes social media features and widgets, such as the Facebook ‘Like’ button, or the ability to ‘tweet this’ or ‘share this,’ as it pertains to articles on our website. These are interactive mini-programs that run on the website. These features may collect a user’s IP address and the page a user visits on the site, and may also set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the eZanga website. A user’s interactions with the Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.

 **Third-Party Links:**

eZanga.com and our subsidiaries contain links to other sites on the Internet. Please be aware that eZanga is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

 **Children’s Privacy:**

eZanga does not knowingly request or collect personally identifiable information, online or offline, from users under 13 years of age or younger. eZanga also does not knowingly use or share personal information from users under 13 years of age with third parties. eZanga complies with all jurisdictional regulations in regards to protecting children's privacy that include GDPR for children residing in the EU under the age of 16.

 **Testimonials or Case Studies:**

eZanga will only post client testimonials and case studies with the client’s consent to do so. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, contact [support@ezanga.com](mailto:support@ezanga.com).

 **Sale of Assets:**

In the event that another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets related to the business of eZanga, we reserve the right to include any or all stored personal information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company.

 **Information Security:**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of data. We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information only in order to operate, develop, or improve our services.

 **Changes to Privacy Policy:**

We reserve the right to amend or revise this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post any changes to this page. 

**Contact eZanga:**

For more information or it you have questions or concerns regarding the eZanga Privacy Policy, please contact [privacy@ezanga.com](mailto:privacy@ezanga.com) or send correspondence to the following address:

eZanga.com, Inc.  
Attn: Data Protection Officer  
222 Carter Drive, Suite 201  
Middletown, DE 19709.  
USA
